{
    "id": "4ffd60eecdc84dd9a91db25e8df608e2",
    "title": "More and more of",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2a29c49a70904e6c94ffcdbeeafdf945",
            "title": "More And More Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I need ……………….. time to finish this job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could I have some ………………… potatoes?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................... students are having to borrow money these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "More",
                        "More of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Two hundred years ago, much ……………… India was covered with trees.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ..................... a fool than I thought.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Three ………………….. the hostages have been rescued.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could I have some …………………. that fried rice?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t think any ………………… them are interested.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is just one ………………….. hurdle to cross.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hate this city ……………….. every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "more of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}